# Chigozie Ofoji

## **Full Stack Software Engineer**

Lagos, Nigeria. 100013 ofojichigozie@gmail.com +234 813 543 9547

Goal-oriented full stack software engineer with over five (5) years work experience in software development. Committed to learning, excellence, ethics, people and striving to achieve the goals of any organization associated with by utilizing technical and innovative skills.

As a full stack engineer, I have worked on a variety of web2.0 and web3.0 products. A telehealth application and event management system are amongst the web2.0 projects. For the web3.0 space, I have worked on staking, farming, launchpad, multisig wallet, vesting, amongst others.

# Work Experience

## **Senior Backend Engineer**

Eventnub - Lagos

December 2022 to February 2023

- · Design and implementation of database schemas
- Design and development of REST API
- Integration of API on frontend application

# **Blockchain Engineer**

Stabledoc - Atlanta, GA

November 2021 to September 2022

- Development of DeFi smart contracts
- Building DApps front-end with React
- Coordinate with colleagues to achieve objectives

#### **Engineering Lead**

Lanepact - Abeokuta, Ogun State.

May 2020 to December 2021

- Organize and monitor technical activities for various projects
- Determine design philosophy and ensure its consistency on projects
- Monitor and provide expert knowledge on tests and technologies
- Coordinate with company project engineers to achieve objectives

#### **Web3 Integration Specialist**

Stabledoc - Atlanta, GA

October 2021 to November 2021

- Development of smart contracts
- Building token payment interface
- · Collaborate with colleagues to achieve objectives

#### **Software Engineer**

Self Employed

November 2017 to October 2021

- Developed web-based, android-based and desktop applications
- Built various prototype hardware systems using Arduino microcontrollers
- Debugged and fixed bugs in various existing software

#### Java Engineer

Storehouse Software Services - Uyo, Nigeria.

December 2020 to February 2021

- Worked with the engineering team in developing inventory management solutions.
- Built the desktop version of the solutions

#### **Web Developer**

Start Innovation Hub - Uyo, Nigeria.

August 2019 to October 2019

- Development of website and web applications as a solution to client's problems
- Enhancing applications by identifying opportunities for improvement, making recommendations, designing and implementing systems
- Maintaining and improving existing codebases and peer review code changes
- Liaising with colleagues to implement technical designs

### **SIWES Internship**

Click Network Solutions - Umuahia, Nigeria.

April 2016 to October 2016

- Collaborated with other interns to install networking and hardware devices
- Developed software to solve pressing issues amongst the interns
- Troubleshoot technical issues and developed solutions as well as reports for validation of proposed solutions

#### Education

# **Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering**

Michael Okpara University of Agriculture

2012 to 2017

#### Skills

- Solidity (3 years)
- Hardhat and Truffle (2 years)
- Ethers.js and Web3.js (2 years)
- Javascript (5 years)
- Node.js (5 years)
- React.js (4 years)
- Typescript (3 years)

- Mongodb (5 years)
- MySQL (5 years)
- Rust (1 year)

# Languages

• English - Fluent

# Links

https://github.com/ofojichigozie

https://www.linkedin.com/in/chigozie-ofoji